shoppingsquare.com.au 2017-06-06

# Online Shopping @ Shopping Square.COM.AU Online Bargain & Discount Shopping Square

### Privacy Policy

We here at ShoppingSquare.com.au value takes your privacy and your privacy concerns seriously. Please read further to understand what how we manage your personal information and how we keep it secure. This policy covers Shopping Square's treatment of your personal information.

**Collecting Personal Information From You.**

Shopping Square automatically receives personally identifiable information from you [the customer] as soon as you register with Shopping Square, these include full name, email and home address. When you register with us, your information is documented in our system. All of this is required for us to be able to conduct a transaction with you online.

Any other personal information that we collect from you is what you tell us about yourself when placing an order or through our customer support ticket system, this personal information is only privy to the current employees of Shopping Square.

Shopping Square will only use your personal information to contact you to conduct an online transaction and to customise the advertising and content on that appears on our website.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure.**

Shopping Square will never disclose your personal information to anyone outside of Shopping Square. 

We will only disclose this information if:

•You have given us your explicit consent  
•We need to share your information in order to procure the product; as reasonably as can be expected.

•That disclosure is required by court orders and legal process.

We do not engage in telephone marketing or unsolicited e-mail marketing. Please do not hesitate to let us know if you do not wish to receive promotional material from us.

**Correcting and Maintaining Your Personal Information.**

Shopping Square allows you to edit any personal information that you consider inaccurate or incorrect at any time. It also allows you to manage your preferences, including whether you wish to be contacted by us about promotional material.

**Security**

Your Shopping Square account is protected by a password for your privacy

We partner with Geotrust to use the latest in Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) 256bit technology so that your privacy remains safe while you are conducting a transaction with us.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to edit our Privacy Policy as we see fit. Any substantial changes to our Privacy Policy will be duly documented in our news page.
